A Guide to the Militia Commission Papers, 1777-1858
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Militia Commissions, 1777-1858., Extent: 66.71 cu. ft. (169 boxes). (Box 3-171)
  - Subseries A. Counties, 1777-1858.
    - Monongalia County, 1815. (Box 99, Folder 24)
    - Monongalia County, 1816. (Box 99, Folder 25)
    - Monongalia County, 1817. (Box 99, Folder 26)
    - Monongalia County, 1818. (Box 99, Folder 27)
    - Monongalia County, 1819. (Box 99, Folder 28)
    - Monongalia County, 1820. (Box 99, Folder 29)
    - Monongalia County, 1821. (Box 99, Folder 30)
    - Monongalia County, 1822. (Box 99, Folder 31)
    - Monongalia County, 1823. (Box 99, Folder 32)
    - Monongalia County, 1824. (Box 99, Folder 33)
    - Monongalia County, 1825. (Box 99, Folder 34)
    - Monongalia County, 1826. (Box 99, Folder 35)
    - Monongalia County, 1827. (Box 99, Folder 36)
    - Monongalia County, 1828. (Box 99, Folder 37)
    - Monongalia County, 1829. (Box 99, Folder 38)
    - Monongalia County, 1830. (Box 99, Folder 39)
    - Monongalia County, 1831. (Box 99, Folder 40)
    - Monongalia County, 1832. (Box 99, Folder 41)
    - Monongalia County, 1833. (Box 99, Folder 42)
    - Monongalia County, 1834. (Box 99, Folder 43)
    - Monongalia County, 1835. (Box 99, Folder 44)
    - Monongalia County, 1836. (Box 99, Folder 45)
    - Monongalia County, 1837. (Box 99, Folder 46)
    - Monongalia County, 1838. (Box 99, Folder 47)
    - Monongalia County, 1839. (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Monongalia County, 1840. (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Monongalia County, 1841. (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Monongalia County, 1842. (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Monongalia County, 1843. (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Monongalia County, 1844. (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Monongalia County, 1845. (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Monongalia County, 1846. (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Monongalia County, 1847. (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Monongalia County, 1848. (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Monongalia County, 1849. (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Monongalia County, 1850. (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Monongalia County, 1851. (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Monongalia County, 1852. (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Monongalia County, 1853. (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Monongalia County, 1856. (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Monongalia County, undated. (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Monroe County, 1799. (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Monroe County, 1800. (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Monroe County, 1801. (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Monroe County, 1802. (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Monroe County, 1803. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Monroe County, 1804. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Monroe County, 1805. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Monroe County, 1806. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Monroe County, 1807. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Monroe County, 1808. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Monroe County, 1809. (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Monroe County, 1810. (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Monroe County, 1811. (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Monroe County, 1812. (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Monroe County, 1813. (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Monroe County, 1814. (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Monroe County, 1815. (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Monroe County, 1816. (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Monroe County, 1817. (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Monroe County, 1818. (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Monroe County, 1819. (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - Monroe County, 1820. (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Monroe County, 1821. (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - Monroe County, 1822. (Box 101, Folder 24)
    - Monroe County, 1823. (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - Monroe County, 1824. (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - Monroe County, 1825. (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - Monroe County, 1826. (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - Monroe County, 1827. (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - Monroe County, 1828. (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - Monroe County, 1829. (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - Monroe County, 1830. (Box 101, Folder 32)
    - Monroe County, 1831. (Box 101, Folder 33)
    - Monroe County, 1832. (Box 101, Folder 34)
    - Monroe County, 1833. (Box 101, Folder 35)
    - Monroe County, 1834. (Box 101, Folder 36)
    - Monroe County, 1835. (Box 101, Folder 37)
    - Monroe County, 1836. (Box 101, Folder 38)
    - Monroe County, 1837. (Box 101, Folder 39)
    - Monroe County, 1838. (Box 101, Folder 40)
    - Monroe County, 1839. (Box 101, Folder 41)
    - Monroe County, 1840. (Box 101, Folder 42)
    - Monroe County, 1841. (Box 101, Folder 43)
    - Monroe County, 1842. (Box 101, Folder 44)
    - Monroe County, 1843. (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Monroe County, 1844. (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Monroe County, 1845. (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Monroe County, 1846. (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Monroe County, 1847. (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Monroe County, 1848. (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Monroe County, 1849. (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Monroe County, 1850. (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Monroe County, 1851. (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Monroe County, 1852. (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Monroe County, 1853. (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Monroe County, 1856. (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Montgomery County, 1782. (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Montgomery County, 1785. (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Montgomery County, 1786. (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Montgomery County, 1787. (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Montgomery County, 1788. (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Montgomery County, 1791. (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Montgomery County, 1793. (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Montgomery County, 1794. (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Montgomery County, 1795. (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Montgomery County, 1796. (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Montgomery County, 1797. (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Montgomery County, 1798. (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Montgomery County, 1799. (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Montgomery County, 1800. (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Montgomery County, 1801. (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Montgomery County, 1802. (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Montgomery County, 1803. (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Montgomery County, 1805. (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Montgomery County, 1807. (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Montgomery County, 1808. (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Montgomery County, 1809. (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Montgomery County, 1810. (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Montgomery County, 1811. (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Montgomery County, 1812. (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Montgomery County, 1813. (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Montgomery County, 1814. (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Montgomery County, 1815. (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Montgomery County, 1816. (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - Montgomery County, 1817. (Box 103, Folder 29)
    - Montgomery County, 1818. (Box 103, Folder 30)
    - Montgomery County, 1819. (Box 103, Folder 31)
    - Montgomery County, 1821. (Box 103, Folder 32)
    - Montgomery County, 1822. (Box 103, Folder 33)
    - Montgomery County, 1823. (Box 103, Folder 34)
    - Montgomery County, 1824. (Box 103, Folder 35)
    - Montgomery County, 1825. (Box 103, Folder 36)
    - Montgomery County, 1826. (Box 103, Folder 37)
    - Montgomery County, 1827. (Box 103, Folder 38)
    - Montgomery County, 1828. (Box 103, Folder 39)
    - Montgomery County, 1829. (Box 103, Folder 40)
    - Montgomery County, 1830. (Box 103, Folder 41)
    - Montgomery County, 1831. (Box 103, Folder 42)
    - Montgomery County, 1832. (Box 103, Folder 43)
    - Montgomery County, 1833. (Box 103, Folder 44)
    - Montgomery County, 1834. (Box 103, Folder 45)
    - Montgomery County, 1835. (Box 103, Folder 46)
    - Montgomery County, 1836. (Box 103, Folder 47)
    - Montgomery County, 1837. (Box 103, Folder 48)
    - Montgomery County, 1838. (Box 103, Folder 49)
    - Montgomery County, 1839. (Box 103, Folder 50)
    - Montgomery County, 1840. (Box 103, Folder 51)
    - Montgomery County, 1841. (Box 103, Folder 52)
    - Montgomery County, 1842. (Box 103, Folder 53)
    - Montgomery County, 1843. (Box 103, Folder 54)
    - Montgomery County, 1844. (Box 103, Folder 55)
    - Montgomery County, 1845. (Box 103, Folder 56)
    - Montgomery County, 1846. (Box 103, Folder 57)
    - Montgomery County, 1847. (Box 103, Folder 58)
    - Montgomery County, 1848. (Box 103, Folder 59)
    - Montgomery County, 1849. (Box 103, Folder 60)
    - Montgomery County, 1850. (Box 103, Folder 61)
    - Montgomery County, 1851. (Box 103, Folder 62)
    - Montgomery County, 1852. (Box 103, Folder 63)
    - Montgomery County, 1853. (Box 103, Folder 64)
    - Montgomery County, undated. (Box 103, Folder 65)
    - Morgan County, 1820. (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Morgan County, 1821. (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Morgan County, 1822. (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Morgan County, 1823. (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Morgan County, 1824. (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Morgan County, 1825. (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Morgan County, 1826. (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Morgan County, 1827. (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Morgan County, 1828. (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Morgan County, 1829. (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Morgan County, 1830. (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Morgan County, 1831. (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Morgan County, 1832. (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Morgan County, 1833. (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Morgan County, 1834. (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Morgan County, 1835. (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Morgan County, 1836. (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Morgan County, 1837. (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Morgan County, 1838. (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Morgan County, 1839. (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Morgan County, 1840. (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Morgan County, 1841. (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Morgan County, 1842. (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Morgan County, 1843. (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - Morgan County, 1844. (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Morgan County, 1845. (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Morgan County, 1846. (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - Morgan County, 1847. (Box 104, Folder 28)
    - Morgan County, 1848. (Box 104, Folder 29)
    - Morgan County, 1849. (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - Morgan County, 1850. (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - Morgan County, 1851. (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - Morgan County, 1852. (Box 104, Folder 33)
    - Morgan County, undated. (Box 104, Folder 34)
    - Nansemond County, 1783. (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Nansemond County, 1785. (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Nansemond County, 1786. (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Nansemond County, 1787. (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Nansemond County, 1788. (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Nansemond County, 1789. (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Nansemond County, 1790. (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Nansemond County, 1791. (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Nansemond County, 1792. (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Nansemond County, 1793. (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Nansemond County, 1794. (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Nansemond County, 1795. (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Nansemond County, 1796. (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Nansemond County, 1797. (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Nansemond County, 1798. (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Nansemond County, 1800. (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Nansemond County, 1802. (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Nansemond County, 1803. (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Nansemond County, 1804. (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Nansemond County, 1805. (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Nansemond County, 1806. (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - Nansemond County, 1807. (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - Nansemond County, 1808. (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - Nansemond County, 1809. (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - Nansemond County, 1811. (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - Nansemond County, 1812. (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Nansemond County, 1813. (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Nansemond County, 1814. (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - Nansemond County, 1815. (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Nansemond County, 1817. (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - Nansemond County, 1818. (Box 105, Folder 31)
    - Nansemond County, 1819. (Box 105, Folder 32)
    - Nansemond County, 1820. (Box 105, Folder 33)
    - Nansemond County, 1821. (Box 105, Folder 34)
    - Nansemond County, 1822. (Box 105, Folder 35)
    - Nansemond County, 1823. (Box 105, Folder 36)
    - Nansemond County, 1824. (Box 105, Folder 37)
    - Nansemond County, 1825. (Box 105, Folder 38)
    - Nansemond County, 1826. (Box 105, Folder 39)
    - Nansemond County, 1827. (Box 105, Folder 40)
    - Nansemond County, 1828. (Box 105, Folder 41)
    - Nansemond County, 1829. (Box 105, Folder 42)
    - Nansemond County, 1830. (Box 105, Folder 43)
    - Nansemond County, 1831. (Box 105, Folder 44)
    - Nansemond County, 1832. (Box 105, Folder 45)
    - Nansemond County, 1833. (Box 105, Folder 46)
    - Nansemond County, 1834. (Box 105, Folder 47)
    - Nansemond County, 1835. (Box 105, Folder 48)
    - Nansemond County, 1836. (Box 105, Folder 49)
    - Nansemond County, 1837. (Box 105, Folder 50)
    - Nansemond County, 1838. (Box 105, Folder 51)
    - Nansemond County, 1839. (Box 105, Folder 52)
    - Nansemond County, 1840. (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Nansemond County, 1841. (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Nansemond County, 1842. (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Nansemond County, 1843. (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Nansemond County, 1844. (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Nansemond County, 1845. (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Nansemond County, 1846. (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Nansemond County, 1847. (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Nansemond County, 1848. (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Nansemond County, 1849. (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Nansemond County, 1850. (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Nansemond County, 1851. (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Nansemond County, 1852. (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Nansemond County, 1853. (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Nansemond County, 1853-1854. (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Nansemond County, 1856. (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Nansemond County, undated. (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Nelson County (Kentucky), 1786-1787. (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Nelson County (Kentucky), 1788. (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Nelson County (Kentucky), 1790. (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Nelson County (Kentucky), 1791. (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Nelson County (Kentucky), 1798. (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Nelson County (Kentucky), 1805. (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Nelson County, 1808. (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Nelson County, 1809. (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Nelson County, 1810. (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Nelson County, 1811. (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Nelson County, 1812. (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Nelson County, 1813. (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Nelson County, 1814. (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Nelson County, 1815. (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Nelson County, 1816. (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Nelson County, 1817. (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - Nelson County, 1818. (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Nelson County, 1819. (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - Nelson County, 1820. (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - Nelson County, 1821. (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - Nelson County, 1822. (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - Nelson County, 1823. (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - Nelson County, 1824. (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - Nelson County, 1825. (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - Nelson County, 1826. (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - Nelson County, 1827. (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - Nelson County, 1828. (Box 107, Folder 27)
    - Nelson County, 1829. (Box 107, Folder 28)
    - Nelson County, 1830. (Box 107, Folder 29)
    - Nelson County, 1831. (Box 107, Folder 30)
    - Nelson County, 1832. (Box 107, Folder 31)
    - Nelson County, 1833. (Box 107, Folder 32)
    - Nelson County, 1834. (Box 107, Folder 33)
    - Nelson County, 1835. (Box 107, Folder 34)
    - Nelson County, 1836. (Box 107, Folder 35)
    - Nelson County, 1837. (Box 107, Folder 36)
    - Nelson County, 1838. (Box 107, Folder 37)
    - Nelson County, 1839. (Box 107, Folder 38)
    - Nelson County, 1840. (Box 107, Folder 39)
    - Nelson County, 1841. (Box 107, Folder 40)
    - Nelson County, 1842. (Box 107, Folder 41)
    - Nelson County, 1843. (Box 107, Folder 42)
    - Nelson County, 1844. (Box 107, Folder 43)
    - Nelson County, 1845. (Box 107, Folder 44)
    - Nelson County, 1846. (Box 107, Folder 45)
    - Nelson County, 1847. (Box 107, Folder 46)
    - Nelson County, 1848. (Box 107, Folder 47)
    - Nelson County, 1849. (Box 107, Folder 48)
    - Nelson County, 1850. (Box 107, Folder 49)
    - Nelson County, 1851. (Box 107, Folder 50)
    - Nelson County, 1852. (Box 107, Folder 51)
    - Nelson County, 1853. (Box 107, Folder 52)
    - Nelson County, undated. (Box 107, Folder 53)
    - New Kent County, 1781. (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - New Kent County, 1785. (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - New Kent County, 1786. (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - New Kent County, 1787. (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - New Kent County, 1788. (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - New Kent County, 1789. (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - New Kent County, 1791. (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - New Kent County, 1792. (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - New Kent County, 1793. (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - New Kent County, 1794. (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - New Kent County, 1795. (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - New Kent County, 1796. (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - New Kent County, 1797. (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - New Kent County, 1798. (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - New Kent County, 1799. (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - New Kent County, 1800. (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - New Kent County, 1801. (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - New Kent County, 1802. (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - New Kent County, 1803. (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - New Kent County, 1804. (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - New Kent County, 1805. (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - New Kent County, 1806. (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - New Kent County, 1807. (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - New Kent County, 1808. (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - New Kent County, 1809. (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - New Kent County, 1810. (Box 108, Folder 26)
    - New Kent County, 1811. (Box 108, Folder 27)
    - New Kent County, 1812. (Box 108, Folder 28)
    - New Kent County, 1813. (Box 108, Folder 29)
    - New Kent County, 1814. (Box 108, Folder 30)
    - New Kent County, 1818. (Box 108, Folder 31)
    - New Kent County, 1819. (Box 108, Folder 32)
    - New Kent County, 1820. (Box 108, Folder 33)
    - New Kent County, 1821. (Box 108, Folder 34)
    - New Kent County, 1822. (Box 108, Folder 35)
    - New Kent County, 1823. (Box 108, Folder 36)
    - New Kent County, 1824. (Box 108, Folder 37)
    - New Kent County, 1825. (Box 108, Folder 38)
    - New Kent County, 1827. (Box 108, Folder 39)
    - New Kent County, 1828. (Box 108, Folder 40)
    - New Kent County, 1829. (Box 108, Folder 41)
    - New Kent County, 1830. (Box 108, Folder 42)
    - New Kent County, 1831. (Box 108, Folder 43)
    - New Kent County, 1832. (Box 108, Folder 44)
    - New Kent County, 1833. (Box 108, Folder 45)
    - New Kent County, 1834. (Box 108, Folder 46)
    - New Kent County, 1835. (Box 108, Folder 47)
    - New Kent County, 1836. (Box 108, Folder 48)
    - New Kent County, 1837. (Box 108, Folder 49)
    - New Kent County, 1838. (Box 108, Folder 50)
    - New Kent County, 1839. (Box 108, Folder 51)
    - New Kent County, 1840. (Box 108, Folder 52)
    - New Kent County, 1841. (Box 108, Folder 53)
    - New Kent County, 1842. (Box 108, Folder 54)
    - New Kent County, 1843. (Box 108, Folder 55)
    - New Kent County, 1844. (Box 108, Folder 56)
    - New Kent County, 1845. (Box 108, Folder 57)
    - New Kent County, 1846. (Box 108, Folder 58)
    - New Kent County, 1847. (Box 108, Folder 59)
    - New Kent County, 1848. (Box 108, Folder 60)
    - New Kent County, 1849. (Box 108, Folder 61)
    - New Kent County, 1850. (Box 108, Folder 62)
    - New Kent County, 1851. (Box 108, Folder 63)
    - New Kent County, 1852. (Box 108, Folder 64)
    - New Kent County, 1853. (Box 108, Folder 65)
    - New Kent County, 1854. (Box 108, Folder 66)
    - New Kent County, 1856. (Box 108, Folder 67)
    - New Kent County, 1858. (Box 108, Folder 68)
    - New Kent County, undated. (Box 108, Folder 69)
    - Nicholas County, 1818. (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Nicholas County, 1819. (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Nicholas County, 1820. (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Nicholas County, 1822. (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Nicholas County, 1823. (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Nicholas County, 1824. (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Nicholas County, 1825. (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Nicholas County, 1826. (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Nicholas County, 1827. (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Nicholas County, 1828. (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Nicholas County, 1829. (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Nicholas County, 1830. (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Nicholas County, 1831. (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Nicholas County, 1832. (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Nicholas County, 1833. (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Nicholas County, 1834. (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Nicholas County, 1835. (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Nicholas County, 1836. (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Nicholas County, 1837. (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Nicholas County, 1839. (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - Nicholas County, 1840. (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - Nicholas County, 1841. (Box 109, Folder 22)
    - Nicholas County, 1842. (Box 109, Folder 23)
    - Nicholas County, 1843. (Box 109, Folder 24)
    - Nicholas County, 1844. (Box 109, Folder 25)
    - Nicholas County, 1845. (Box 109, Folder 26)
    - Nicholas County, 1846-1847. (Box 109, Folder 27)
    - Nicholas County, 1848. (Box 109, Folder 28)
    - Nicholas County, 1849. (Box 109, Folder 29)
    - Nicholas County, 1850. (Box 109, Folder 30)
    - Nicholas County, 1851. (Box 109, Folder 31)
    - Nicholas County, 1852. (Box 109, Folder 32)
    - Nicholas County, 1853. (Box 109, Folder 33)
    - Nicholas County, 1856. (Box 109, Folder 34)
    - Norfolk County, 1784. (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Norfolk County, 1785. (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Norfolk County, 1786. (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Norfolk County, 1787. (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk County, 1788. (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Norfolk County, 1790. (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Norfolk County, 1791. (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Norfolk County, 1792. (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Norfolk County, 1793. (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Norfolk County, 1794. (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Norfolk County, 1795. (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Norfolk County, 1796. (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Norfolk County, 1797. (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Norfolk County, 1798. (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Norfolk County, 1799. (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Norfolk County, 1800. (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Norfolk County, 1801. (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Norfolk County, 1802. (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Norfolk County, 1803. (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Norfolk County, 1804. (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Norfolk County, 1805. (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Norfolk County, 1806. (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Norfolk County, 1807. (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Norfolk County, 1808. (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Norfolk County, 1809. (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Norfolk County, 1810. (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - Norfolk County, 1811. (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - Norfolk County, 1812. (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - Norfolk County, 1813. (Box 110, Folder 29)
    - Norfolk County, 1814. (Box 110, Folder 30)
    - Norfolk County, 1815. (Box 110, Folder 31)
    - Norfolk County, 1816. (Box 110, Folder 32)
    - Norfolk County, 1817. (Box 110, Folder 33)
    - Norfolk County, 1818. (Box 110, Folder 34)
    - Norfolk County, 1819. (Box 110, Folder 35)
    - Norfolk County, 1820. (Box 110, Folder 36)
    - Norfolk County, 1821. (Box 110, Folder 37)
    - Norfolk County, 1822. (Box 110, Folder 38)
    - Norfolk County, 1823. (Box 110, Folder 39)
    - Norfolk County, 1824. (Box 110, Folder 40)
    - Norfolk County, 1825. (Box 110, Folder 41)
    - Norfolk County, 1826. (Box 110, Folder 42)
    - Norfolk County, 1827. (Box 110, Folder 43)
    - Norfolk County, 1828. (Box 110, Folder 44)
    - Norfolk County, 1829. (Box 110, Folder 45)
    - Norfolk County, 1830. (Box 110, Folder 46)
    - Norfolk County, 1831. (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Norfolk County, 1832. (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Norfolk County, 1833. (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Norfolk County, 1834. (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk County, 1835. (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Norfolk County, 1836. (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Norfolk County, 1837. (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Norfolk County, 1838. (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Norfolk County, 1839. (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Norfolk County, 1840. (Box 111, Folder 10)